New York Civil Liberties Union; Records apap331
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The New York Civil Liberties Union Records1998 December 5 - 2017 June 3
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
New York Civil Liberties Union
apap331
700 715 Captures
The New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) is the preeminent statewide organization dedicated to the protection and enhancement of individual civil liberties and civil rights in New York State. Founded in 1951, the NYCLU’s mission is to defend and uphold the basic rights and liberties articulated in the Bill of Rights and to advocate, litigate and educate for the protection of civil liberties. Through litigation, legal counsel, advocacy and legislative lobbying, the NYCLU has, among many issues, protected political freedom during the McCarthy era, argued against the constitutionality of the Vietnam War, created the first project focused on the rights of mentally disabled, and was the first civil liberties organization to advocate for reforming the foster care placement system. Over the last thirty years, the NYCLU has advocated for issues surrounding voting rights and censorship, fought to end gender discrimination and school segregation in New York State schools, and defended the separation of church and state. The collection consists of legal case files, administrative records and other archival materials. The collection is being processed and is currently closed, unless permission to access is granted in writing from the NYCLU Executive Director.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information. Certain restrictions may apply.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives. 2013
Historical Note
The New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) was founded in November 1951 as the New York affiliate of the American Civil Liberties Union, it is not-for-profit, nonpartisan organization with nearly 50,000 members across New York State. The stated mission of the organization is defend and promote New Yorkers’ unalienable rights, including freedom of speech and religion, and the right to privacy, equality and due process of law. NYCLU performs its work through litigation, advocacy, community organizing, and public education.
The NYCLU has eight chapters in New York State: Central New York, the Capital Region, Lower Hudson Valley, Suffolk County, Nassau County, New York City, Genesee Valley and the Western Region. The New York City office is the organization’s headquarters and represents all regions that do not have their own local chapter or regional office.
Scope and Contents
This collection predominantly consists of the thousands of legal case files the NYCLU partook in. The legal case files series spans from freedom of speech, religion, press, petition, and assembly, to privacy, to equality before and due process of law. The legal cases show the expansive service the NYCLU performs for underrepresented groups and person of New York State.
The Executive Director files contain the material of past Executive Directors, the NYCLU Board, including board meeting minutes, and chapter news. The legislative Committee series tracks the work of the NYCLU and their impact advocating for New Yorkers through reform. In 1970, a campaign led by the NYCLU's legislative office lead to the repeal of a state law that imposes criminal sanctions for the performance of medical abortions.
The advocacy series represents the tireless work to promote the issues of New Yorkers including, military and selective service, reproductive rights, LBGT rights, racial justice, immigrants’ rights, rights of people with disabilities, voting rights, youth and student rights, and women and equality. Subject Files show the day to day aspects of the NYCLU and include memorandum of staff attorneys. As well as general subject based materials.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is partially processed. Individual items may be difficult to find.
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Civil Rights; Legal briefs; New York (State). Court of Appeals; Law (discipline); Legal Files; Web Archives; Wages -- New York (State); Glasser, Ira; Neier, Aryeh, 1937-; American Civil Liberties Union; New York Civil Liberties Union
- NYCLU Website, 1998 December 5 - 2017 June 3; 1; 715 captures
  URL
  https://www.nyclu.org/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: New York Civil Liberties Union
  created_date: 2016-02-29T19:49:16Z
  created_by: gwiedeman
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:57Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1998 December 5
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1999 January 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1999 February 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1999 April 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1999 October 13
    Scope and Contents
    Meta tag for description: The NYCLU is a statewide organization dedicated to the protection and enhancement of New Yorkers' civil liberties as enumerated in the Bill of Rights of the U.S. Constitution and the Constitution of the State of New York.
    Meta tag for keywords: NYCLU, New York, NYC, civil liberties, constitution, bill of rights
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2000 March 2
    Meta tag for keywords: NYCLU, ACLU, New York, NYC, civil liberties, american civil liberties union, new york civil liberties union, constitution, bill of rights, freedom of speech, first amendment, free speech
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 May 10
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 June 3
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 July 7
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 August 15
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 November 10
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 November 18
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2000 December 3
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2001 February 2
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2001 March 1
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2001 March 31
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2001 April 18
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2001 September 22
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2001 November 30
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 March 28
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 March 30
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 June 4
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 June 6
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 July 18
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 August 2
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 September 23
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 September 28
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 October 14
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 October 28
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 November 4
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 November 21
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 November 26
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2002 November 28
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 January 24
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 February 3
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 February 14
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 February 16
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 March 25
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 April 10
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 April 24
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 April 26
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 May 24
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 May 29
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 June 21
    Meta tag for description: The NYCLU, the New York State affiliate of the American Civil Liberties Union, is a statewide organization dedicated to the protection and enhancement of New Yorkers' civil liberties as enumerated in the Bill of Rights of the U.S. Constitution and the Constitution of the State of New York.
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 July 21
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 August 4
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 August 8
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 September 28
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 October 12
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 November 25
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 December 4
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 December 15
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2003 December 25
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2004 January 13
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2004 March 26
  - NYCLU: New York Civil Liberties Union Front Page, 2004 April 15
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 May 20
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 May 26
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 June 8
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 June 10
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 June 24
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 July 18
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 July 26
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 August 11
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 August 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 August 30
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 August 31
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 September 5
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 September 12
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 September 24
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 October 16
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 November 2
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 November 16
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 December 8
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 December 11
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2004 December 18
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 January 23
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 January 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 February 4
  - 502 Bad Gateway, 2005 February 6
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 February 10
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 February 11
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 February 20
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 February 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 February 26
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 March 3
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 March 31
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 April 4
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 April 20
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 May 7
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 May 18
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 May 21
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 June 2
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 June 5
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 June 9
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 June 10
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 July 20
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 August 6
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 August 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 August 27
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 August 28
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 August 31
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 October 24
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 November 4
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 November 5
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 November 9
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 November 27
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 November 30
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 December 5
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 December 8
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 December 19
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2005 December 26
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 January 3
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 January 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 January 30
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 February 2
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 February 2
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 February 7
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 March 4
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 April 7
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 April 15
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 April 27
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 May 17
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 June 13
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 June 15
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 July 1
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 August 10
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 August 15
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 August 20
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 August 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 August 30
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 September 29
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 October 3
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 October 9
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 October 12
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 October 18
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 October 26
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 November 2
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 November 9
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 November 16
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 November 23
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 November 30
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 December 5
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 December 6
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 December 8
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 December 13
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 December 13
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2006 December 31
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 January 5
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 January 10
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 January 20
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 January 25
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 February 1
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 February 24
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 March 4
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 April 13
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 May 27
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 June 7
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 June 10
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 June 29
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 August 4
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 August 17
  - NYCLU Front Page, 2007 August 21
  - NYCLU, 2007 September 26
  - NYCLU, 2007 October 2
  - NYCLU, 2007 October 4
  - NYCLU, 2007 October 5
  - NYCLU, 2007 October 7
  - NYCLU, 2007 October 10
  - NYCLU, 2007 October 11
  - NYCLU, 2007 November 8
  - NYCLU, 2007 November 10
  - NYCLU, 2007 December 11
  - NYCLU, 2008 January 10
  - NYCLU, 2008 February 16
  - NYCLU, 2008 March 18
  - NYCLU, 2008 April 18
  - NYCLU, 2008 May 9
  - NYCLU, 2008 May 12
  - NYCLU, 2008 May 16
  - NYCLU, 2008 June 5
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 3
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 4
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 6
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 7
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 10
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 12
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 14
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 15
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 16
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 17
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 18
  - 502 Bad Gateway, 2008 July 19
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 20
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 21
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 23
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 24
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 25
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 26
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 27
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 28
  - NYCLU, 2008 July 29
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 3
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 4
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 7
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 8
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 9
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 10
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 11
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 12
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 13
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 15
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 16
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 17
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 18
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 19
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 20
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 21
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 22
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 23
  - NYCLU, 2008 August 27
  - NYCLU, 2008 September 3
  - NYCLU, 2008 September 9
  - NYCLU, 2008 October 10
  - NYCLU, 2008 October 22
  - NYCLU, 2008 October 29
  - NYCLU, 2008 November 6
  - NYCLU, 2008 November 8
  - NYCLU, 2008 November 10
  - NYCLU, 2008 November 12
  - NYCLU, 2008 November 19
  - NYCLU, 2008 November 26
  - NYCLU, 2008 December 21
  - NYCLU, 2009 January 24
  - NYCLU, 2009 January 24
  - NYCLU, 2009 February 16
  - NYCLU, 2009 February 24
  - NYCLU, 2009 February 28
  - NYCLU, 2009 March 5
  - NYCLU, 2009 March 19
  - NYCLU, 2009 March 24
  - NYCLU, 2009 March 26
  - NYCLU, 2009 May 25
  - NYCLU, 2009 June 20
  - NYCLU, 2009 July 21
  - NYCLU, 2009 August 22
  - not present, 2009 September 22
  - NYCLU, 2009 October 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2009 November 8
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2009 November 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2009 December 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2009 December 29
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 January 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 January 29
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 February 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 February 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 March 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 March 13
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 March 24
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 April 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 April 17
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 April 18
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 April 23
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 May 8
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 May 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 June 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 July 7
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 July 17
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 July 23
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 July 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 August 5
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 August 18
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 September 18
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 October 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 October 22
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 November 5
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 November 8
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 November 23
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2010 December 24
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 January 3
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 January 15
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 January 26
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 January 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 February 5
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 February 12
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 February 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 March 10
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 March 14
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 April 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 May 2
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 May 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 June 1
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 June 2
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 June 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 July 7
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 July 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 July 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 July 19
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 July 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 July 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 August 9
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 August 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 September 1
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 September 6
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 September 17
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 September 23
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 September 27
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 October 6
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 October 23
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 November 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2011 December 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2012 January 6
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2012 January 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2012 January 14
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2012 January 17
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2012 January 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) - American Civil Liberties Union of New York State, 2012 January 23